<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="mal"><![CDATA[Malnutrition is a group of conditions in children and adults generally related to poor quality or insufficient quantity of nutrient intake, absorption, or utilization. There are two major types of malnutrition:\n • Protein-energy malnutrition - resulting from deficiencies in any or all nutrients \n• Micronutrient deficiency diseases - resulting from a deficiency of specific micronutrients \n \n Protein-energy malnutrition There are three types of protein-energy malnutrition in children:\n 1.Acute malnutrition\n Appearance:Wasting or thinness\n Cause:Acute inadequate nutrition leading to rapid weight loss or failure to gain weight normally\n 2.Chronic malnutrition\n Appearance: Stunting or shortness\n Cause Inadequate nutrition over long period of time leading to failure of linear growth\n 3.Acute and chronic malnutrition\n Appearance:Underweight\n Cause:A combination measure, therefore, it could occur as a result of wasting, stunting, or both\n Wasting and stunting are very different forms of malnutrition. Stunting is chronic and its causative factors are poorly understood. Stunting usually does not pose an immediate threat to life and is relatively common in many populations in less-developed countries. This is not to say that it is unimportant, just less important than wasting in humanitarian emergencies. Wasting results from an acute shortage of food, is reversible with refeeding, and has a relatively high mortality rate. For these reasons, wasting is the highest priority form of malnutrition in humanitarian emergencies.Each form of malnutrition depends on what nutrients are missing in the diet, for how long and at what age. The most basic kind is called protein energy malnutrition . It results from a diet lacking in energy and protein because of a deficit in all major macronutrients, such as carbohydrates, fats and proteins. Marasmus is caused by a lack of protein and energy with sufferers appearing skeletally thin. In extreme cases, it can lead to kwashiorkor, in which malnutrition causes swelling including a so-called \'moon face\'. Other forms ...]]></string>
</resources>

