<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VacciMe</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vaccines">Vaccines</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nutrition">Nutrition</string>
    <string name="nutrition">Early initiation of breastfeeding \n\nProportion of children born in the last 24 months who were put to the breast within one hour of birth.\n\n Minimum diet diversity\n\n Proportion of children ages 6-23 months who receive foods from four or more food groups. The food groups used for calculation of this indicator were: grains, roots and tubers; legumes and nuts; dairy products (milk, yogurt, cheese); flesh foods (meat, fish, poultry and liver/organ meats); eggs; vitamin-A rich fruits and vegetables; other fruits and vegetables. \n\nMinimum meal frequency \n\nProportion of breastfed and non-breastfed children 6-23 months of age who receive solid, semi-solid, or soft foods (but also including milk feeds for non-breastfed children) the minimum number of times or more. Minimum for breastfed children is defined as two times for ages 6-8 months and three times for 9-23 months. For non-breastfeed children minimum is four times for ages 6-23 months.\n\n Minimum acceptable diet\n\n Proportion of breastfed children 6-23 months of age who had at least minimum dietary diversity and minimum meal frequency and non-breastfed children 6-23 months of age who received at least two milk feedings and had minimum diet diversity (not including milk feeds) and minimum meal frequency.</string>
    <string name="haem">Haemophilus influenzae type B is a Gram-negative bacterium that causes meningitis and acute respiratory infections and severe neurological sequelae. It is an important cause of pneumonia in young children.Others H. influenzae disease include epiglottitis, osteomyelitis, septic arthritis and septicaemia.Haemophilus influenzae type b be can be prevented by vaccination. Children should get a Hib vaccine at: 2 months; 4 months; 6 months; 12 through 15 months</string>
    <string name="dpr_org">DPT refers to combination of vaccines against three infectious diseases : diphtheria, pertussis (whooping cough), and tetanus. Diphtheria is a severe bacterial infection that causes a thick covering in the back of your mouth and throat. Pertussis causes periods of rapid coughing with no break. This makes it hard to eat, drink, or breathe. Tetanus is a severe infection caused by bacteria found in dirt, manure, and dust. Tetanus may cause painful muscle spasms and lockjaw.\n The DTP vaccine is only given to children younger than 7 years. Children usually get 5 doses of the DTP vaccine between 6 weeks and 6 years: \n The first dose at 2 months; \n The second dose at 4 months; \n The third dose at 6 months; \n The fourth dose at 15 to 18 months; \n The fifth dose at 4 to 6 years</string>
    <string name="polio_org">Polio is a highly infectious viral disease, which mainly affects young children.It invades the nervous system and can cause irreversible paralysis in a matter of hours.There is muscle weakness resulting in an inability to move. There is no cure for polio, it can only be prevented by immunization.However, a number of doses are required for it to be effective. Children get 4 doses of IPV at these ages: 2 months, 4 months, 6-18 months, and a booster dose at 4-6 years.</string>
    <string name="hepb">Hepatitis B is a serious disease caused by a virus called hepatitis B virus (HBV)that attacks the liver, can cause lifelong infection, cirrhosis (scarring) of the liver, liver cancer, liver failure, and death.Hepatitis B vaccine is available to prevent HBV infection.\n\n Hepatitis B vaccine (HepB) usually is given as a series of three injections:\n shortly after birth ;\n at 1–2 months of age ;\n at 6–18 months of age</string>
</resources>
